http://www.msd.com/policy/terms-of-use/home.html

Skip to content
Terms of Use
These terms were last revised on August 3, 2020.
This website is maintained by Merck Sharp & Dohme Corp., a subsidiary of Merck & Co., Inc., Kenilworth, New Jersey, U.S.A. and is intended for use by residents outside of the U.S. and its territories and Canada who are 18 years of age or older.
By using this website, you agree to be bound by, and to comply with, the terms of use on this page (“Terms of Use”). MSD reserves the right to change the Terms of Use from time to time, as necessary, and will provide notice, on this page, of any such changes, including the date they became effective. You may access this page at any time through the Terms of Use link at the bottom of each page on this website.
Nothing on this website should be construed as the giving of advice or the making of a recommendation regarding any decision or action related to your health or the health of others.  If you are a patient, you should consult a doctor or other qualified health care professional regarding any questions you have about your health or before making any treatment decisions. If you are a doctor or other qualified health care professional, you should not allow the content of this website to substitute for your own medical judgment, which you should exercise in evaluating the information on this website.
While it has used reasonable efforts to ensure that the information on this website is accurate, complete, and current, MSD expressly disclaims any warranty or representation regarding the accuracy, completeness, or currency of such information. THE INFORMATION ON THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED “AS IS,” WITHOUT A WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT.
On this website MSD may collect, through registration processes or other means, personal information about you. Please refer to MSD’s Global Internet Privacy Policy for details about how we protect your personal information as well as MSD’s Global Online Tracking Policy regarding the types of cookies and similar technologies that our websites, web applications and other online services use and how you can control cookies on your computer or mobile device. You are responsible for the accuracy of any personal information about you that you provide to MSD through this website.
Except for information covered by our privacy policy, any communication or materials you transmit to or through the website, including data, comments, questions, suggestions, ideas, concepts, know-how, techniques, or the like, shall become the property of MSD. MSD shall be free to use, disclose, reproduce, or distribute any such communications or materials without limitation of any kind.
This website may contain information brought to you by third parties or through links to other Internet websites. Notice of information or links of this kind is provided throughout the website. MSD does not control nor assume any responsibility for the information provided by third parties or the content of other Internet websites to which we provide links.
This website may include “forward-looking statements” within the meaning of the safe harbor provisions of the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995.
MSD undertakes no obligation to publicly update any forward-looking statement, whether as a result of new information, future events, or otherwise. Additional factors that could cause results to differ materially from those described in the forward-looking statements can be found in MSD’s most recent Annual Report on Form 10-K and the company’s other filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) available at www.sec.gov.
You should assume that all trademarks, logos, designs, slogans, and trade dress appearing on this website, whether or not appearing in large print, italics, or with the trademark symbol, are owned by MSD or its affiliate companies, or are used under license. This website may also contain or reference patents, proprietary information, technologies, products, processes, or other proprietary rights of MSD and/or other parties. No license to, or right in, any such trademarks, patents, trade secrets, technologies, products, processes, and other proprietary rights of MSD and/or other parties is granted to, or conferred upon, you.
You may not distribute, modify, transmit, reuse, repost, or use the content of the website for public or commercial purposes, including the text, images, audio, or video, without the written permission of MSD. You should assume that everything you see or read on this website is copyrighted unless otherwise noted and may not be used, except as provided in the Terms of Use or in the text on the website, without the written permission of MSD. MSD neither warrants nor represents that your use of materials displayed on the website will not infringe rights of third parties not owned by, or affiliated with, MSD.
Pursuant to Section 230 of the federal Communications Decency Act, providers of interactive computer services shall not be treated as the publisher or speaker of any information provided by another information content provider. Although MSD may from time to time monitor or review discussions, chats, postings, transmissions, bulletin boards, and the like on the website, if any, MSD is under no obligation to do so and assumes no responsibility or liability arising from the content of any such Web pages or utilities nor for any third party’s error, defamation, libel, slander, omission, falsehood, obscenity, pornography, profanity, danger, or inaccuracy contained in any information within such pages or utilities on the website. You are prohibited from posting or transmitting any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, scandalous, inflammatory, pornographic, or profane material or any material that could constitute or encourage conduct that would be considered a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any law.
MSD reserves the right, if you violate the Terms of Use, to suspend or terminate any account you have created on this website.
